[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
705 emails.
That madman hasn't stopped.
How are you?
We're doing fine here.
Wake up, please?
I made a tiny altar in memory of Marco.
Hello, Marco.
They told me, “Give up, Drake.”
“She's moved on.”
But hell, I won't.
[singing] Happy birthday, happy birthday.
You said you love me.
I'm holding you to that, Alys.
He could hear, he could feel.
We were surprised that he finally woke up now.
Gabby, I'm off.
Bye, Tommy.
Hey, are you going to see him again?
Mhm!
Bye, Kevs!
Bye.
Where do you live again?
Pampanga.
Right, Pampanga.
What's your favorite food?
Adobo.
Really?
Adobo?
It has been months since you woke up.
And...
you seem okay.
I'm just happy to see you okay.
That you're living your life.
Without me.
But I’m still scared to approach you.
I don't know
how you'll react if we ever meet again.
I don't know if you'll let me back into your life.
So...
that's why I'm happy watching you from afar.
I promised myself,
I’d only come back to the Philippines when you wake up.
But I don't know.
There's still a hole in my heart that I need to fill.
- Miss. - Hello!
- Excuse me. - Here's your Newyork cheesecake.
Your iced latte.
And for you, sir...
Your hot double shot americano.
- Enjoy! - God, service is so slow.
Yes, sir?
How may I help you?
Everything cool, Alys?
Tripp?
Hey.
Zy!
You can move.
How about a coffee?
You know what, Zy?
I’ve been sleeping in the hospital for three years.
You're still as slow as ever.
What's wrong with you?
I've been looking for you.
Tofer told me that you worked here.
So, I came to see you.
Aren't you mad at me?
Can I still do something about it?
I’m sorry.
Zy...
Zy!
I'm doing fine.
Don't worry, okay?
It’s enough for me that the years you’ve lost
were meant to watch over me.
Thank you.
It's the least that I can do.
Alys...
You're free now.
Do whatever you want to do.
I know in my heart that
I held you for so long.
Because I love you.
But I know who truly makes you happy.
So, go.
Go back to Drake.
Don't wait for me.
Huh?
But...
Zy!
You did nothing wrong.
I have never blamed you.
I am not blaming you.
I will never blame you.
Remember what I told you?
You should always be happy, right?
Do you remember?
Okay?
Good.
Don't be stubborn.
Go back to Drake.
I’m okay now.
Go back inside.
I've taken up enough of your time.
No, no!
Tripp!
You can talk as much as you want.
You can talk the entire day!
That's okay!
I don’t mind.
As long as I have proof that you’re alive.
You're breathing.
You’re talking. You’re smiling.
Tell me anything.
I’m contented with that.
I'm real.
You believe me now?
By the way,
my mom told me that
you'd only go back to the Philippines when I get better.
Start packing, okay?
- Alright, bye. - Damn it, Tripp!
Ouch!
Come on!
You still have the nerve to joke around?
Do you want to send me back to the hospital?
Sorry.
You really seem mad at me.
By the way,
I'm going back to New York.
My flight’s tonight.
I just came to say goodbye.
What about your job here?
Have you been stalking me?
Anyway,
I'll be going.
Don't you want to try our coffee?
Just for a bit. Come on!
Go on, Silly.
They're looking for you already.
Your customers might get mad.
But I know who truly makes you happy.
So, go.
Go back to Drake.
I hope he hasn't changed his number yet.
Alys...
Drake?
I’ve waited for years.
Tripp said it himself.
I should go back to the one who truly makes me happy.
I'm coming home.
To you.
Turn around.
Aren’t you going to hug me?
I freaking love you, Drake Sebastian Palma!
I thought it would go away after all the pain that you've caused me.
But the more I distance myself from you,
the more I find myself looking for you.
I freaking love you.
Bad words.
I freaking love you!
I freaking, freaking, freaking love you!
Okay.
I get it.
I believe you.
I love you to the moon and back.
Marry me.
But this time,
I want to do it in front of God,
and the people we love.
I want to see you walk the aisle
while I wait for you at the end.
It feels so good to hear that, Drake.
After everything that happened in our story,
you’re still the one I’ll come home to.
So, is that a yes?
A yes to what?
To forever.
With me.
Yes, Drake.
To the moon and back.
But...
But what?
But this time, we need to do it right.
No one will get hurt anymore.
No more dragging anyone else into this.
I think we all deserve to be happy.
Alys...
Can you be mine?
Again?
Please?
Hey.
Why do you look like you’re about to be executed?
I'm just kidding.
I’m just trying to make you guys laugh.
You look so serious.
So, now what?
This is it?
We just stare at each other all day?
- Sorry. - Sorry.
Wow.
You even answer at the same time now!
But, seriously.
Sorry for what?
- For everything. - For everything.
You know what?
You guys look stupid.
Don’t you know that?
Do you believe in the saying,
“Everything happens for a reason”?
Because for me, I do.
I don’t know if I’m just saying that to make myself feel better
about what happened to me.
About what happened to all of us.
But I believe that...
everything happens for a reason.
I believe that...
I’m not just some insignificant part of all this.
That I was put in your story...
so that we could all get to this point.
To the ending where,
finally,
you both know for certain that you’re meant to be together.
That’s why you should never apologize to me.
It happened because it had to.
I don't regret anything.
To be honest,
I'm the one who should be sorry.
Drake...
You were right.
Somehow, someway,
I was the reason why you two broke up.
To be fair,
I was really concerned for you.
And aside from the fact that...
I loved you.
But, it didn't work out.
But I'll admit it.
I just hated the idea that...
you'd win again.
You’ll get ahead of me again.
That you’ll be the one chosen again.
Remember what I told you?
That you were ruining Alys.
And I'm sorry.
Things went spiral from there.
You know, after everything that happened to me...
The accident.
That was my karma.
I deserved it.
Drake.
Take care of Alys, okay?
Alys.
Be happy.
Please.
Alys, did you not hear what I said?
Come on, you’ve been crying all the way to the end.
Seriously, enough already.
So?
I guess, that’s it.
I'll go ahead.
I've been asleep for three years.
I've got a lot to catch up on.
See you in the Philippines?
Tripp!
Uh, guys.
This is Amber.
My friend.
Amber, this is Drake, Alys.
Alys, Drake, Amber.
Hello, Amber.
Hi, Amber.
Hi, guys.
So?
I guess I'll see you.
We'll go ahead.
- Already? - Right now?
We still have our afternoon walk.
Alright. Let’s go.
- Bye. - Bye.
Take care.
Ready?
Let's go home.
Travel the world. Have a tour package.
I made this in memory of Marco.
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry I wasn’t able to take care of you.
That’s why you’re not with us now.
Sorry, I wasn’t able to visit you right away.
I just wanted your mommy to be okay when she comes back.
Just know that I love you.
I love you very much.
You'll always be my Baby Marco.
My little angel.
Emma, that's your Daddy Drake.
The one I showed you in the pictures.
This one.
Daddy!
That's your daddy, yes!
That's right!
He's a good dad, you know.
We agreed on co-parenting.
He respected it when I asked for space.
He never bothered us.
But he still kept showing up in the ways he could.
He sends her gifts.
Checks in.
More than enough for the child.
So, they've never met before but they're already that close?
Right?
He was in the U.S. for the most part when our daughter was growing up.
But, only from afar.
I tested him but he still kept coming back.
He's serious about being a father.
I felt sorry for him because he kept on going to the U.S.,
but I don't let him get close to our daughter.
But, I also knew
that he wasn't there solely for our child.
What do you mean?
He fought hard to stop himself from seeing you, Alys.
He was very much aware that you needed your space.
So, he waited.
And lucky for him,
by the time he couldn't help himself from going,
you were ready to open up again.
The proposal.
All in good time, right?
Yes.
You're lucky, Alys.
You got to see him grow at the same time his love for you did.
And by the way, congratulations on your engagement.
Thank you.
Well, technically,
re-engagement.
They're so cute.
Right?
They look alike.
- True. - Very much alike.
She looks like you too.
Really?
Mhm.
Thank you.
What a long day.
It's my best friend's big day tomorrow.
It's a long time coming.
I still got a lot to do.
Bestie, why don't you just type those up?
Aya, she just wants it to be more personal.
Hey!
Are you going to fight again?
Where are the flowers and butterflies?
They're still not here.
Even the guests are not complete.
When will they be complete?
Alys!
Don't stress yourself.
Everything will be fine.
Yeah, you know what?
Why don't you just give me that checklist?
Kei and I will take care of it.
Sure?
Yeah, of course.
What's the point of having bridesmaids if you're going to do everything yourself?
Wow, how about the maid of honor?
You know what?
You're so sensitive.
Not everything's about you.
Okay, before you guys start fighting again.
Let’s just go, Shaira.
What?
I'm not starting a fight.
I'm just concerned.
She's pregnant.
I don't want her to be stressed out.
Are you guys sure?
Sounds like you're already fighting.
Bestie, stop micromanaging.
Trust us, Alys.
You're going to have the most perfect wedding ever!
And we'll take care of the butterflies!
Yes.
- So, let's go? - Let’s go?
Let's go.
- Oh, after that we could take a dip in the pool! - Thank you, girls!
Bestie,
I'm sorry.
I know I'm your maid of honor
but it's like...
I wasn’t much help.
Come on, Bestie.
Don't worry about it. It's fine!
Bestie?
I'm really happy for you.
You’ve waited so long for this.
I wish this to be your happy ever after.
What's with the face?
Nothing.
Bestie?
I don't really know.
I mean, we’re okay.
I’m doing great. Drake and I are fine.
But?
But it's like...
I’m the one who’s not sure about this.
I don't understand myself.
Shouldn't I be happy?
I don't know why I'm thinking about this.
That's normal, Bestie.
Wedding jitters.
It’s more than just feeling nervous.
A lot of things will change.
A lot of things in my life will change.
I mean, the first time Drake and I got married,
I didn't put in much thought.
Then everything happened.
Look at where it got us.
That's true.
And if I make this decision, there's no going back.
Bestie, there's always a choice.
But you wouldn't let it get to that.
Maybe I'm just afraid that...
I won't be enough.
For Drake?
Or...
for the life that I'm getting myself into.
Bestie, you don't have to be perfect.
Drake isn't marrying you because you're perfect.
He's marrying you for you.
Thank you, Bestie.
My maid of honor.
Yes.
And my godchild.
Relax.
You've been like this for a while.
Are you stressed at work?
This isn’t work.
Then, what’s that?
You've been on that laptop for a while.
Yes, but not for work.
What's that for?
You've been there for a while.
Hello?
My vow.
Your vows?
Why are you doing your vows?
Didn't we agree to be spontaneous?
Because.
Because what?
Alys, can you stop asking questions?
Just leave it, okay?
And we're back with grumpy Drake again.
Come on.
You know how annoying I am, right?
I'll annoy you more and more.
Come on, what is it?
What is it?
Fine!
I’m scared I’ll blank out on the day of the wedding.
And I'll ruin the whole ceremony.
Hmm?
You? Stuttering?
The Drake Palma I know doesn’t stutter.
As if.
You have no idea what you do to me, Alys.
On the wedding day,
seeing you with that white gown,
and you smiling at me.
That alone is enough to leave me speechless.
You're madly in love with me.
You have no idea how much I love you.
Yes, I do have an idea how much you love me.
To the moon and back.
Yes, Alys.
I'll marry you anywhere, baby.
I mean,
I'll marry you
as long as you are the bride and I'm the groom.
You deserve everything.
The gown.
The venue.
And all the preparations.
Alys, I'm willing to give you everything.
I’ve waited so long for this day.
And you are worth waiting for.
I love you.
1131.
Always and forever.
Forever.
Hi, Mom.
I'm going to remarry Alys today.
Remember Alys?
The noisy...
Annoying...
Sassy...
And a troublesome woman.
But you know what?
She's strong.
Independent.
Brave.
And she’s not one to give up easily.
She loves with her whole heart.
Forgives even when it's hard.
She puts the people she loves first.
And she became a woman who knows exactly what she wants.
And what she deserves.
This time, Mom,
I won't let her go.
Too bad you're not here with me right now.
So you can see how happy I am.
I miss you, mom.
Come in.
Ready?
Drake, can I go first?
I was the one who approached you first, right?
Do you remember that time when
I randomly approached you and declared that
Drake Palma!
You're my boyfriend now!
I didn’t do it because I liked you or loved you.
I did it
for the person I loved during that time.
And I think you know that.
Yes.
You were the one who approached first.
I'm Alys!
Alys Zyril Perez, soon to be Palma.
Hello!
But it just means that you were the brave one.
You’ve always been the braver one between the two of us.
I thought that challenge would be easy.
But you...
You were the difficult one, Drake.
You were cold.
Quiet.
Grumpy.
What?
You were very hard to read, Drake.
In your dreams.
You're ugly.
Very unpredictable.
We’re here now, Alys.
I never thought we’d make it this far.
Bird brain.
You’re harsh!
Noob!
My noob!
I never thought someone like you would accept me.
You're annoying.
But that's fine.
But through it all,
I knew you.
All of you.
In the midst of all my fears,
all the fights,
and goodbyes...
You became my constant.
I got to know the real you.
Not the man you show to others,
but the man you are when no one is watching.
Drake?!
Shh!
The quiet ways you care,
the words you rarely utter,
but cut deep.
I'm territorial.
Every imperfection.
Every side.
The happy ones.
Wait!
That’s too much!
The annoying ones.
What's with the skimpy attire?
Pardon me?
The sides that I'm scared of.
Alys, what do you mean what's my deal?
The sides that are so hard to understand.
Where are we going?
What do you mean?
Why are you here?
Feeling close?
Are we close?
Alys...
We were pretty close.
We were exes, remember?
We used to hug.
We used to —
What do you want, Drake?
We hurt each other.
We broke up.
We got tired so many times.
We gave up.
Drake!
You will regret this, Drake Palma!
Drink and forget.
Drink until you forget.
After all the fights we’ve been through,
settled on,
and everything we’ve been through.
Drake,
if you love me,
please stop this.
Please.
Let me go.
We should let go of each other.
But we found our way back to each other.
Damn you, Palma!
Yeah.
Damn me.
Even after being apart for so long,
there’s one thing that never changed.
And that's my love for you, Drake.
I love you so much, Alys.
I can’t promise you that we’ll never face challenges again.
But I promise you,
no matter what challenges we face, I’ll never leave your side.
On the easy days,
and especially the hard ones.
On the days we’re certain,
and the days we’re not.
I know we had a rocky start,
but I'm sure
that God destined you to be with me.
We're here now, Alys.
One thing is certain.
I can't live without you by my side, my noob.
There's only one thing
I can promise you.
I will always, always choose you.
Because I always find my way back home to you.
Through it all, Drake...
my Drakey baby,
I'll always be your noob,
your bird brain,
your little Alys who loves you very, very, very much, Drake.
To the moon and back.
Just as you promised me,
I will always
love you to the moon and back, Alys Zyril Perez.
I love you,
Drake Sebastian Jimenez Palma.
I'm the luckiest man in the world.
Because I have you.
I love you.
My noob.
Alys,
take this ring
as a symbol of my love,
commitment
and the promise of all my tomorrows.
Drake,
take this ring
as a symbol of all my love and vows
for all that I am and all that I have.
I honor you.
By the power vested in me, I pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may now kiss the bride.
Oh!
Drake, be careful.
From dating Alys Perez to marrying Alys Perez...
Done!
Seducing Drake Palma...
Mission accomplished!
3, 2, 1...
Action!
Good morning!
Go in!
Dana and Andy did a great job on the papers and essay.
Alys and Andy did a great job on the papers...
and the essay —
Alys, Tripp still has a line.
Distance makes the heart grow...
...stronger?
You stand noisily!
She already knows how to drive!
Let’s give Rabin a round of applause!
[singing] And if we make it to the end...
The book already closed!
Sheen is getting all flustered.
Get out!
Is that right?
Third wheel!
My nose is bleeding.
[singing]
Are you crying?
Oh, I don’t have a teaser of the next episode!
It's a wrap!
Thank you, guys!
Thank you, DAP Team. It’s a wrap.